{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Range Hood Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/62002/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62002,"taskName":"Range Hood Install","taskDescription":"Install a Range Hood","xmTaskDescriptor":"Range Hood Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":140,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"hood, vent, range, fan, ventilation, stove","textMessagingName":"Hood Install","rolloverLongDesc":"Some range hoods will need to vented to the exterior of the house.  Some blow the air back into the kitchen after filtering it.","rolloverShortDesc":"Installing a ventilation hood above a range","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install a Range Hood.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Range Hood Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Kitchen Vent Install","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":3,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Kitchen Vent Hood Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Range Hood - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Vent Hood Project","urlName":"Range-Hood-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Kitchen Range Hood Installation Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"hood, vent, range, fan, ventilation, stove","emcCategoryOid":-12003,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":8408,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62002/":{"taskOID":62002,"originalTaskOID":62002,"setID":8408,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":502626,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of installation is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of installation is this?","shortQuestionText":"What kind of installation is this?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":203553,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New range hood in a new location","answerDisplayText":"New range hood in a new location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203554,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace old range hood in same location","answerDisplayText":"Replace old range hood in same location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502627,"questionDisplayText":"Is the new hood vented?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is the new hood vented?","shortQuestionText":"Is the new hood vented?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":203555,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":" Yes, the hood is vented to the exterior","answerDisplayText":" Yes, the hood is vented to the exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203556,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No, the hood is ventless (vents back into the kitchen)","answerDisplayText":"No, the hood is ventless (vents back into the kitchen)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200054,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Not sure - Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Not sure - Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502628,"questionDisplayText":"Have you already purchased the range hood?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased the range hood?","shortQuestionText":"Have you already purchased the range hood?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":502626,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of installation is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of installation is this?","shortQuestionText":"What kind of installation is this?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":203553,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New range hood in a new location","answerDisplayText":"New range hood in a new location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203554,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace old range hood in same location","answerDisplayText":"Replace old range hood in same location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":203553,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New range hood in a new location","answerDisplayText":"New range hood in a new location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203554,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace old range hood in same location","answerDisplayText":"Replace old range hood in same location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502627,"questionDisplayText":"Is the new hood vented?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is the new hood vented?","shortQuestionText":"Is the new hood vented?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":203555,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":" Yes, the hood is vented to the exterior","answerDisplayText":" Yes, the hood is vented to the exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203556,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No, the hood is ventless (vents back into the kitchen)","answerDisplayText":"No, the hood is ventless (vents back into the kitchen)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200054,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Not sure - Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Not sure - Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":203555,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":" Yes, the hood is vented to the exterior","answerDisplayText":" Yes, the hood is vented to the exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203556,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No, the hood is ventless (vents back into the kitchen)","answerDisplayText":"No, the hood is ventless (vents back into the kitchen)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200054,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Not sure - Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Not sure - Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502628,"questionDisplayText":"Have you already purchased the range hood?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased the range hood?","shortQuestionText":"Have you already purchased the range hood?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}